Guide to the Stanford University Video Collection SC1031
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Videos
  - Introduction to CMS/XEDIT (Part II); Ray Peck; Stanford Instructional Television Network/Stanford University. Academic Information Resources., 1989-6-15; V470; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
    VM/CMS; XEDIT; Stanford University. Stanford Instructional Television Network
  - Introduction to the X Window System; George D. Drapeau; Stanford Instructional Television Network/Stanford University. Academic Information Resources., 1989; V471; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
    X Window System (Computer system); Stanford University. Stanford Instructional Television Network
  - Introduction to TOPS-20; Daniel Zappala; Stanford Instructional Television Network/Stanford University. Academic Information Resources., 1989-6-15; V472; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
    Operating systems (Computers); Stanford University. Stanford Instructional Television Network
  - UNIX I; Stanford Instructional Television Network/Stanford University. Academic Information Resources., V473; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
    Stanford University. Stanford Instructional Television Network
  - UNIX II; Stanford Instructional Television Network/Stanford University. Academic Information Resources., 1989-3-7; V474; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - "Introduction to the Tresidder Macintosh Cluster, Including a Basic Introduction to the Macintosh." Stanford Instructional Television Network/Stanford University. Academic Information Resources., 1989-6-15; V475; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
    Macintosh, use of; Stanford University. Stanford Instructional Television Network
  - Symbolic Systems I, Part 1, 1987-1-12; V476.1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
    Barwise, Jon.
  - Symbolic Systems I, Part 2, 1987-1-26; V476.2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Symbolic Systems I, Part 3, 1987-2-2; V476.3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Symbolic Systems I, Part 4, 1987-2-2; V476.4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Symbolic Systems I, Part 5, 1987-2-23; V476.5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Symbolic Systems I, Part 6, 1987-3-2; V476.6
  - Symbolic Systems I, Part 7, 1987-3-4; V476.7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Symbolic Systems I, Part 8, 1987-3-9; V476.8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Chicano/a Studies Program, Center for Comparative Studies in Race and Ethnicity, El Centro Chicano & Stanford Alumni Association. Eighteenth Annual Ernesto Galarza Commemorative Lecture by Luis Valdez, 2003; V477.1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Chicano/a Studies Program, Center for Comparative Studies in Race and Ethnicity, El Centro Chicano & Stanford Alumni Association. Eighteenth Annual Ernesto Galarza Commemorative Lecture by Luis Valdez, 2003; V477.2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Matt Phillips: The Magic In His Prints, Stanford University Libraries, 2001; V478; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
    Phillips, Matt, 1927-
  - Catalysis "Technology for a Clean Environment", 1993; V479; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
    Produced for Council for Chemical Research by Bo Boudart Films and Video
  - Stanford Reunion Video [Class of 1945, 1948 or 1950?], undated; V480; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Gift of Isabella Donna Zappettini, 2016. (ARCH-2017-058)
  - Computer Science: Winograd Et Al…, 1990-11-10; V481; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - CS "Japan Symposium" Tape 1, undated; V482; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - CS "Japan Symposium" Tape 2, undated; V483; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - EE380 Allison, 1988-6-1; V484; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - EE380 Allison, 1988-1-20; V485; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - The Stanford Computer Science Video Journal: Artificial Intelligence Research Lectures: Is There a Standard AI Paradigm? Terry Winograd, undated; V486; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Paul Edwards, Hector Garcia-Molina, undated; V487; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Mobile Computing: Mary Baker, 2000-5-9; V488; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Computer Security: Dan Bonen, undated; V489; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Terry Winograd-CSDV Project, undated; V490; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Hector Garcia-Molina, undated; V491; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Computer Security: John Mitchell, undated; V492; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - The CIS Program in Advanced System Technologies for High-Speed Computing, undated; V493; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - John McCarthy, undated; V494; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Eric Roberts Interview and Tour, undated; V495; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Unlabeled, undated; V496; 3 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Faculty Talent Show, V497-V499; 3 videotape(s) (u-matic)
  - Cross-Cultural (Ethnic) Theme Houses at Stanford University: Contributing to the Undergraduate Experience, 1993-6; V500; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
  - Okada & Teahouse Origins, 2009-10-25; V501; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
  - DFJ Entrepreneurial Thought Leaders: Spring 2004: John Hennessy: Stanford University: Stanford University: The Wellspring for Silicon Valley, 2004 Apr 21; V502; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - InterChange: John Hennessy, 1997 Feb; V503; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Stanford Executive Briefings: Creating the Revolution: John Hennessy, 1998; V504; 2 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Philip Fialer Memorial Services, 2014 Jun 6; V505; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
    Fialer, Phil
  - Seashore oddities, 2008; V506; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
    Hopkins Marine Station; Grover, John
  - Anne T. and Robert M. Bass: An Uncommon Legacy, V507
    Uncommon Man Award; Uncommon Woman Award; Bass, Robert M.; Bass, Anne T.
  - Golden Gate International Exposition, 1939; V508; 2 optical disc(s) (dvd)
  - Inauguration of Marc Tessier-Lavigne, 2016-10-21; V509; 1 computer file(s) (mov)
    The inauguration ceremony for Marc Tessier-Lavigne, 11th president of Stanford University, was be held on Friday, Oct. 21 from 9:30 to 11 a.m. in Laurence Frost Amphitheater.
  - Frosh on the Farm: First Impressions of Stanford, 2000; V510; 2 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Big Game Movies, V511
    Teaser Trailer; Saturday; Flicks Trailer; Sun - Car Day 1, Mon - Hoover Day 2; Tue - Dining Hall Day 3; Wed - Bike Day 4; Thu - Quad Day 5 (plus edited version); Fri - Fountain Day 6.
  - The Stanford Magazine...A Step Ahead, V512; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic)
  - Stanford Football, 2015-2016; V513; 3 optical disc(s) (dvd)
    Stanford vs. Notre Dame (W, 38-36), Saturday, Nov. 28, 2015, Stanford Stadium; 2015 Pac-12 Football Championship Game, Stanford vs. USC (W, 41-22), Saturday, Dec. 5, 2015, Levi's Stadium; 102nd Rose Bowl Game, Stanford vs. Iowa (W, 45-16), Friday, Jan. 1, 2016, Rose Bowl Stadium.
  - Director's Cut with coach Jim Harbaugh, 2007; V514; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
  - Stanford 24, USC 23, 2007; V515; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - 2011 Discover Orange Bowl: The Official Complete Game Broadcast, 2011 Jan 3; V516
  - Stanford in Washington: From the Pacific to the Patomac, Stanford in Washington at 20, 2007 Oct; V517
  - "'What Were They Thinking?' Originalism, Music and the Constitution: A discussion and demonstration of originalism in music and law, with faculty from Stanford University and members of the St. Lawrence String Quartet.", 2006; V518
  - A World of Change: The International Initiative at Stanford University., 2005; V519
  - KTEH and Stanford University present Bill Gates in Conversation with John Hennessy, 2002 Apr 25; V520; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Trustees Demo Reel: Peter Robinson VP Debates, Newshour; Mark Zoback Earthquakes, CNN Channels 2, 5, 7; Larry Diamond, Charlie Rose on Iraq, 2004 Oct 6; V521; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - The Campaign for Undergraduate Education at Stanford (CUE), 2001; V522; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Discover Stanford, undated; V523; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Nike/KGO/ABC7 Stacey Hendler (Etchemendy), 2001 Apr 4; V524; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Gerhard Casper Steps Down (6 segments), 1999 Sep 14; V525; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Casper Tribute Video, 2000 Jun 8; V526; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Trustees' Demo, 2004 Feb 9; V527; 1 videotape(s) (VHS)
  - Seizing Power: The Steel Seizure Case Revisited, 2003; V528; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
  - The Search for Jane's Cold Cream Jar, 2003; V529; 1 optical disc(s) (cd-rom)
  - Interview with President John Hennessy, 2015 Jul 23; V530; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
  - Anxious Times: Seeing Beyond a World of Perpetual Threats, 2006 Oct 14; V531; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
  - Stanford Video: Annual Reports, 2004-2005; V532; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
  - Think Again National Tour, 2001-2002; V533; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)